

Profile

Olwethu Mkhuhlane

Passionate programmer with 6 years of experience. Started as a student at the University

circumstances. Took on a Software development and Web Development bootcamp with

Hyperion Development. I am currently a student intern at Explore Data Science Academy,

of the Western Cape for 4 years, could not finish the course due to unforeseen

Student Intern

Cape Town, South Africa olwethumkhuhlane@gmail.com

Details

4361 Oliver Tambo

Street

Cape Town, 7750, South

Africa

0620878533

Date / Place of birth

25 March 1996 Western Cape

Nationality

South African

Employment History

which lasts until the end of the year 2020.

Jan 2020 — Dec 2020

Cape Town

Student Intern at Explore Data Science

Academy

Currently am a Student Intern at Explore Data Science Academy,

contract ends end of year 2020.

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Apr 2019 - Oct 2019

Student Intern at Hyperion Development

Cape Town
Was a student Intern at Hyperion and Cogramma doing Software

development and web development(Full Stack).

Skills

Python

Java

Jan 2019 — Mar 2019

Cape Town Technical Support at iiNet

Gave Australian customers technical support with their

Customer Service representative and

connection setup and troubleshooting.

Node.JS

JavaScript(ES5, ES6)

ReactJS

Heroku

Nov 2018 — Jan 2019

Customer Service at Amazon

Cape Town

Worked for 8 weeks under a seasonal contract. Gave customers

help general retail and technical issues.

JQuery

Bootstrap 4

HTML & CSS

MySQL

Express.js

Education

 $\mathrm{Feb}\ 2014 - \mathrm{Nov}\ 2017$

University of the Western Cape

Cape Town

BSc Computer Science

Studied Computer Science (Extended tream[4 years]) until my 3rd year. Could not complete degree due to financial difficulties.

Jan 2009 - Nov 2013

Sophumelela High School — Matric,

Cape Town

Mathematics and Science

References

Explore Data Science Academy

Nuri Barnard

nuri@explore-ai.net

Life Coach

Hisman Sean Collard

0829550050

Hyperion Dev

Imraan Meyer

imraanm@hyperiondev.com 071 754 4675